<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <template id="report_clx_contract_document">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-call="web.internal_layout">
                <img alt="aaaa" src="/clx_invoice_reports/static/src/images/contract_template_img.png"
                     style="display: block;margin-left: auto;margin-right: auto;width: 50%;"
                     class="img img-responsive"/>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <div t-field="doc.partner_id.name"
                     style="margin-left: 370px;color:#c02023;"/>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <div>
                    <span style="margin-left: 290px;color:#c02023">Dedicated Account Representative Information:</span>
                    <br/>
                    <span style="margin-left: 350px;color:#c02023">Name:</span>
                    <span style="color:#c02023" t-field="doc.partner_id.account_user_id.name"/>
                    <br/>
                    <span style="margin-left: 350px;color:#c02023">Email:</span>
                    <span style="color:#c02023" t-field="doc.partner_id.account_user_id.email"/>
                    <br/>
                    <span style="margin-left: 350px;color:#c02023">Phone:</span>
                    <span style="color:#c02023" t-field="doc.partner_id.account_user_id.phone"/>
                    <br/>
                </div>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p style="text-align:center;">
                    <span t-field="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                    <span>- Proposal of Services</span>
                </p>
                <hr/>
                <table style="width: 100%;">
                    <t t-foreach="doc.order_line" t-as="line">
                        <tbody>
                            <tr>
                                <td>
                                    <t t-esc="line.product_id.name"/>
                                </td>
                                <td/>
                                <td align="right" style="border: 1px solid black;padding: 20px;">Monthly total :
                                    <br/>
                                    <t t-esc="line.price_unit"/>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td/>
                                <td>aaaaaaaaaaaaaa</td>
                                <td/>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td colspan="3">
                                    <hr style="width:50%;text-align:left;margin-left:0"/>
                                </td>
                                <!--<td rowspan="2"><hr style="width:50%;text-align:left;margin-left:0"/></td>
                                <td rowspan="2"><hr style="width:50%;text-align:left;margin-left:0"/></td>-->
                            </tr>
                        </tbody>
                    </t>
                </table>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <div style="border: 2px dotted">
                    <span style="margin-left: 450px;">First Month Spend :
                        <span t-field="doc.amount_total"/>
                    </span>
                </div>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <div style="border: 2px dotted">
                    <span style="margin-left: 450px;">Recurring Monthly Spend :
                        <span t-field="doc.amount_total"/>
                    </span>
                </div>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p style="text-align:center;">Key Information</p>
                <div style="border-style: dotted;">
                    <table style="width: 100%;border: 1px solid #ddd;">
                        <tbody>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Community Name:</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Name of Community name</td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Community address:</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Name of Community address</td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Website:</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Website</td>
                            </tr>
                        </tbody>
                    </table>
                </div>
                <br/>
                <p style="text-align:center;">Length and Fees</p>
                <div style="border-style: dotted;">
                    <table style="width: 100%;border: 1px solid #ddd;">
                        <tbody>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Contract Length</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Contract Length</td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Intended Launch Date::</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Intended Launch Date:</td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Setup Fees:</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Fees</td>
                            </tr>
                        </tbody>
                    </table>
                </div>
                <br/>
                <p style="text-align:center;">Payment Details</p>
                <div style="border-style: dotted;">
                    <table style="width: 100%;border: 1px solid #ddd;">
                        <tbody>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Payment Method:</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Direct Bill</td>
                            </tr>
                        </tbody>
                    </table>
                </div>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p style="text-align:center;">MASTER SERVICES AGREEMENT:</p>
                <br/>
                <p>By signing Conversion Logix Insertion Order(s) that references this Master Services
                    Agreement (together, the Insertion Order(s) and this Master Services Agreement are the
                    “Agreement”), the entity identi ed on said Insertion Order
                    <strong>
                        <span t-field="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                    </strong>
                    and Conversion
                    Logix, LLC (“Provider”) each signi es that it has read, understands, and agrees to be bound
                    by the terms and conditions hereof. Provider and Customer may be referred to
                    individually as a “Party” and collectively as the “Parties.” For good and valuable
                    consideration, the receipt and su ciency of which are hereby acknowledged, the Parties
                    agree to these terms and conditions through their undersigned authorized
                    representatives.
                </p>
                <p>
                    1. <strong>DEFINITIONS.</strong> Capitalized terms used herein shall have the meanings set forth in
                    this
                    Section 1.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>1.1. Aggregated Data</strong>
                    means Personal Information and usage information that is
                    anonymized and aggregated with similar data and information to the extent that the
                    original Personal Information and usage information is no longer attributable to any
                    specific individual.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>1.2. Authorized Persons</strong>
                    means Provider’s employees, contractors, agents, and
                    auditors who have a need to know or otherwise access Personal Information to enable
                    Provider to perform its obligations under this Agreement, and who are bound by
                    con dentiality and other obligations su cient to protect Personal Information in
                    accordance with the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>1.3. Personal Information</strong>
                    means information that Customer provides or for which
                    Customer provides access to Provider, or information which Provider creates or obtains
                    on behalf of Customer, in accordance with this Agreement that: (i) directly or indirectly
                    identi es an individual; or (ii) can be used to authenticate an individual.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>1.4. Data Breach</strong>
                    means any act or omission that materially compromises the security,
                    con dentiality, or integrity of Personal Information or the physical, technical,
                    administrative, or organizational safeguards put in place by Provider, or by Customer
                    should Provider have access to Customer’s systems, that relate to the protection of the
                    security, con dentiality, or integrity of Personal Information, or (ii) receipt of a complaint
                    in relation to the privacy and data security practices of Service Provider or a breach or
                    alleged breach of this Agreement relating to such privacy and data security practices.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>1.5. Losses</strong>
                    mean all losses, damages, liabilities, de ciencies, actions, judgments,
                    interest, awards, penalties, nes, costs, or expenses of whatever kind, including
                    reasonable attorneys’ fees and the cost of enforcing any right to indemni cation
                    hereunder and the cost of pursuing any insurance providers.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.PERFORMANCE OF SERVICES.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.1. Services.</strong>
                    Provider will provide services (“Services”) and works, materials, or other
                    tangible or intangible property (“Deliverables”) to Customer in accordance with the terms
                    and conditions of this Agreement and one or more insertion orders (each an “Insertion
                    Order”) that may be agreed to and executed by the Parties, each of which will be made a
                    part of this Agreement and each of which will contain the applicable rates for the Services
                    and Deliverables set forth therein. This Agreement and any Insertion Orders entered into
                    hereunder constitute the entire agreement between the Parties concerning the subject
                    matter hereof and supersede any other prior or contemporaneous communications. In
                    the event of a con ict between the terms of this Agreement and any Insertion Order, the
                    terms of this Agreement will control unless the Insertion Order explicitly states otherwise.
                    The terms of any purchase order or any general terms and conditions Customer may
                    maintain will not apply. This Agreement does not obligate either Provider or Customer to
                    enter into any speci c Insertion Order or any Insertion Orders at all.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.2. Acceptance.</strong>
                    Except to the extent a Insertion Order contains speci c acceptance
                    provisions, all Services and/or Deliverables provided to Customer for approval will be
                    deemed accepted (“Accepted”) if within ten (10) days after delivery, Customer has not
                    provided to Provider written notice identifying speci cally any basis for not approving the
                    Services and/or Deliverables, as applicable.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.3. Correction/Re-Performance.</strong>
                    If a Service or Deliverable contains any
                    nonconformities, Customer shall describe to Provider in writing the issues with such
                    Service or Deliverable. Provider shall promptly and proactively correct the nonconformity
                    and redeliver the Service or Deliverable or re-perform the activities related to the Service
                    or Deliverable, as the case may be, unless Customer expressly states in writing that it
                    does not require Provider to correct a certain nonconformity that it considers, in
                    Customer’s sole discretion, to be immaterial.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.4. Change Orders.</strong>
                    Changes to the scope of the Services or any Deliverables shall be
                    made only in a writing executed by authorized representatives of both Parties. Provider
                    will not be obligated to work on a change until the Parties agree in writing upon its price
                    and/or schedule impact. Provider will continue performing the Services in according with
                    such Insertion Order until the Parties agree in writing to any such change or adjustment. If
                    the Parties are unable to agree to a mutually acceptable change or adjustment, either
                    Party may terminate the relevant Insertion Order upon ten (10) days’ written notice to the
                    other.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.5. Personnel; Subcontractors.</strong>
                    Provider reserves the right to determine which of its
                    personnel shall be assigned to perform Services; provided, however, that it will, subject to
                    scheduling and sta ng considerations, attempt to honor Customer’s request for speci c
                    individuals. Provider may use subcontractors to perform Services, in which case it will be
                    responsible for the performance of those subcontractors.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p>
                    <strong>3. CUSTOMER OBLIGATIONS.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>3.1. Cooperation.</strong>
                    Customer acknowledges that Provider’s ability to deliver the Services
                    depends upon full and timely cooperation by Customer and Customer’s sta , as well as
                    the timely access to and accuracy and completeness of any information provided.
                    Provider will have no liability for any delay in the provision of Services or other loss of any
                    nature resulting from any failure by Customer to provide full and timely cooperation or to
                    provide Provider accurate and complete information.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>3.2. Compliance with Laws.</strong>
                    Customer shall at all times comply with all federal, state,
                    and local laws, ordinances, regulations, and orders that are applicable to the operation of
                    its business and to this Agreement and its performance hereunder. Without limiting the
                    generality of the foregoing, Customer shall at all times, at its own expense, obtain and
                    maintain all certi cations, credentials, authorizations, licenses, and permits necessary to
                    conduct its business relating to the exercise of its rights and the performance of its
                    obligations under this Agreement. Customer is responsible for providing complete,
                    truthful, and legally compliant information to Provider, and Provider shall not be held
                    responsible for any non-compliance by Customer.
                </p>
                <strong>4. PAYMENT; FEES; EXPENSES.</strong>
                <p>
                    <strong>4.1. Fees.</strong>
                    As full and complete compensation for performing all Services speci ed in
                    this Agreement and for assuming all duties, responsibilities, and obligations required by
                    this Agreement, Customer will compensate Provider for all fees, compensation, and other
                    amounts as speci ed in the applicable Insertion Order (the “Fees”) in accordance with the
                    terms of this Agreement and in any Insertion Order entered into by the Parties. Fees are
                    exclusive of taxes, levies, duties, governmental charges and expenses (with the exception
                    of any Subcontractor’s income taxes), which amounts will be billed to and paid by
                    Customer.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>4.2. Expenses.</strong>Customer shall pay Provider for the reasonable expenses including,
                    but
                    not limited to, out of pocket travel and living expenses, incurred by Provider and its
                    personnel in connection with its performance of the Services (the “Expenses”).
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>4.3. Billing and Payment.</strong>
                    Provider shall prepare and submit invoices to the Customer
                    via email for all Services and expenses incurred on a monthly basis, or as otherwise set
                    forth in the Insertion Order. Customer will pay invoices in U.S. prior to the service start
                    date noted on Provider’s invoice. Payments due hereunder must be made by wire
                    transfer, certi ed check, bank check or such other method as may be agreed upon by the
                    Provider. Customer shall have no right of o set or withholding under this Agreement. Any
                    amounts not paid by Customer when due to Provider shall be subject to interest charges,
                    from the date due until paid, at the rate of one and one half percent (1.5%) per month, or
                    the highest interest rate allowable by law (whichever is less), payable monthly.
                    If any amounts due to Provider from Customer becomes past due for any reason,
                    Provider may at its option and without further notice withhold further Services until all
                    invoices have been paid in full, and such withholding of Services shall not be considered a
                    breach or default of any of Provider’s obligations under this Agreement.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p>
                    <strong>4.4. Taxes.</strong>
                    Provider is responsible for all Provider personnel and for the payment of
                    their compensation, including, if applicable, withholding of income taxes, and the
                    payment and withholding of social security and other payroll taxes, unemployment
                    insurance, workers’ compensation insurance payments, and disability bene ts. Customer
                    shall be responsible for all sales, use, and excise taxes, and any other similar taxes, duties,
                    and charges of any kind imposed by any federal, state, or local governmental entity on
                    any amounts payable by Customer hereunder.Any such taxes, duties, and charges currently assessed or
                    which may be assessed in the
                    future, that are applicable to the Services are for the Customer’s account, and Customer
                    hereby agrees to pay such taxes; provided, that, in no event shall Customer pay or be
                    responsible for any taxes imposed on, or with respect to, Provider’s income, revenues,
                    gross receipts, personnel, or real or personal property or other assets.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>4.5. Disputes.</strong>
                    In the event of any good faith dispute with regard to a portion of an
                    invoice, the undisputed portion shall be paid as provided herein. Upon resolution of the
                    disputed portion, any amounts owed to Provider shall be paid with interest at the rate set
                    forth below accruing from the date such amounts were originally due.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>5. CONFIDENTIALITY.</strong>
                    From time to time during the Term of this Agreement, either Party
                    (as the “Disclosing Party”) may disclose or make available to the other Party (as the
                    “Receiving Party”) information about its business a airs, products/services, con dential
                    intellectual property, trade secrets, third-party con dential information and other
                    sensitive or proprietary information, whether orally or in written, electronic or other form
                    or media, and whether or not marked, designated or otherwise identi ed as “con dential”
                    (collectively, “Con dential Information”). Con dential Information shall not include
                    information that, at the time of disclosure: (i) is or becomes generally available to and
                    known by the public other than as a result of, directly or indirectly, any breach of this
                    Section 5 by the Receiving Party or any of its representatives; (ii) is or becomes available to
                    the Receiving Party on a non-con dential basis from a third-party source, provided that
                    such third party is not and was not prohibited from disclosing such Con dential
                    Information; (iii) was known by or in the possession of the Receiving Party or its
                    representatives before being disclosed by or on behalf of the Disclosing Party; (iv) was or
                    is independently developed by the Receiving Party without reference to or use, in whole
                    or in part, of any of the Disclosing Party’s Con dential Information; or (v) is required to be
                    disclosed under applicable federal, state or local law, regulation or a valid order issued by
                    a court or governmental agency of competent jurisdiction. The Receiving Party shall: (A)
                    protect and safeguard the con dentiality of the Disclosing Party’s Con dential
                    Information with at least the same degree of care as the Receiving Party would protect its
                    own Con dential Information, but in no event with less than a commercially reasonable
                    degree of care; (B) not use the Disclosing Party’s Con dential Information, or permit it to
                    be accessed or used, for any purpose other than to exercise its rights or perform its
                    obligations under this Agreement; and (C) not disclose any such Con dential Information
                    to any person or entity, except to the Receiving Party’s representatives who need to know
                    the Con dential Information to assist the Receiving Party, or act on its behalf, to exercise
                    its rights or perform its obligations under the Agreement.
                    The Receiving Party shall be responsible for any breach of this Section 5 caused by any of
                    its representatives. At any time during or after the term of this Agreement, at the
                    Disclosing Party’s written request, the Receiving Party shall promptly return, and shall
                    require its representatives to return to the Disclosing Party all copies, whether in written,
                    electronic or other form or media, of the Disclosing Party’s Con dential Information, or
                    destroy all such copies and certify in writing to the Disclosing Party that such Con dential
                    Information has been destroyed. In addition to all other remedies available at law, the
                    Disclosing Party may seek equitable relief (including injunctive relief) against the Receiving
                    Party and its representatives to prevent the breach or threatened breach of this Section 5
                    and to secure its enforcement.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>

            </t>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="report_contract_clx">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
                <t t-call="clx_invoice_reports.report_clx_contract_document" t-lang="doc.partner_id.lang"/>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>
