<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <template id="report_clx_contract_document">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-call="clx_invoice_reports.contract_internal_layout">
                <img alt="aaaa" src="/clx_invoice_reports/static/src/images/contract_template_img.png"
                     style="display: block;margin-left: auto;margin-right: auto;width: 50%;"
                     class="img img-responsive"/>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <div t-field="doc.partner_id.name"
                     style="margin-left: 370px;color:#c02023;"/>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <div>
                    <span style="margin-left: 290px;color:#c02023">Dedicated Account Representative Information:</span>
                    <br/>
                    <span style="margin-left: 350px;color:#c02023">Name:</span>
                    <span style="color:#c02023" t-field="doc.partner_id.account_user_id.name"/>
                    <br/>
                    <span style="margin-left: 350px;color:#c02023">Email:</span>
                    <span style="color:#c02023" t-field="doc.partner_id.account_user_id.email"/>
                    <br/>
                    <span style="margin-left: 350px;color:#c02023">Phone:</span>
                    <span style="color:#c02023" t-field="doc.partner_id.account_user_id.phone"/>
                    <br/>
                </div>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p style="text-align:center;">
                    <span t-field="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                    <span>- Proposal of Services</span>
                </p>
                <hr/>
                <table style="width: 100%;">
                    <t t-foreach="doc.order_line" t-as="line">
                        <tbody>
                            <tr>
                                <td>
                                    <t t-esc="line.product_id.name"/>
                                </td>
                                <td/>
                                <td align="right" style="border: 1px solid black;padding: 20px;">Monthly total :
                                    <br/>
                                    <t t-esc="line.price_unit"/>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td/>
                                <td><t t-esc="line.product_id.description"/></td>
                                <td/>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td colspan="3">
                                    <hr style="width:50%;text-align:left;margin-left:0"/>
                                </td>
                                <!--<td rowspan="2"><hr style="width:50%;text-align:left;margin-left:0"/></td>
                                <td rowspan="2"><hr style="width:50%;text-align:left;margin-left:0"/></td>-->
                            </tr>
                        </tbody>
                    </t>
                </table>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <div style="border: 2px dotted">
                    <span style="margin-left: 450px;">First Month Spend :
                        <span t-field="doc.amount_total"/>
                    </span>
                </div>
                <br/>
                <br/>
                <div style="border: 2px dotted">
                    <span style="margin-left: 450px;">Recurring Monthly Spend :
                        <span t-field="doc.amount_total"/>
                    </span>
                </div>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p style="text-align:center;">Key Information</p>
                <div style="border-style: dotted;">
                    <table style="width: 100%;border: 1px solid #ddd;">
                        <tbody>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Community Name:</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">
                                    <span t-field="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                                </td>
                            </tr>

                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Community address:</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">
                                    <span t-field="doc.partner_id"
                                          t-options="{&quot;widget&quot;: &quot;contact&quot;, &quot;fields&quot;: [&quot;address&quot;, &quot;phone&quot;], &quot;no_marker&quot;: True, &quot;phone_icons&quot;: True}"/>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Website:</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">
                                    <span t-field="doc.partner_id.website"/>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                        </tbody>
                    </table>
                </div>
                <br/>
                <p style="text-align:center;">Length and Fees</p>
                <div style="border-style: dotted;">
                    <table style="width: 100%;border: 1px solid #ddd;">
                        <tbody>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Contract Length</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">
                                    <span t-field="doc.contract_length"/>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Intended Launch Date::</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">
                                    <span t-field="doc.intended_launch_date"/>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Setup Fees:</td>
                                <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">
                                    <span t-field="doc.setup_fee"/>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                        </tbody>
                    </table>
                </div>
                <br/>
                <t t-if="doc.payment_term_id">
                    <p style="text-align:center;">Payment Details</p>
                    <div style="border-style: dotted;">
                        <table style="width: 100%;border: 1px solid #ddd;">
                            <tbody>
                                <tr>
                                    <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">Payment Method:</td>
                                    <td style="border-bottom: 1px dashed red;">
                                        <span t-field="doc.payment_term_id.name"/>
                                    </td>
                                </tr>
                            </tbody>
                        </table>
                    </div>
                </t>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p style="text-align:center;">MASTER SERVICES AGREEMENT:</p>
                <br/>
                <p>By signing Conversion Logix Insertion Order(s) that references this Master Services
                    Agreement (together, the Insertion Order(s) and this Master Services Agreement are the
                    “Agreement”), the entity identi ed on said Insertion Order
                    <strong>
                        <span t-field="doc.partner_id.name"/>
                    </strong>
                    and Conversion
                    Logix, LLC (“Provider”) each signi es that it has read, understands, and agrees to be bound
                    by the terms and conditions hereof. Provider and Customer may be referred to
                    individually as a “Party” and collectively as the “Parties.” For good and valuable
                    consideration, the receipt and su ciency of which are hereby acknowledged, the Parties
                    agree to these terms and conditions through their undersigned authorized
                    representatives.
                </p>
                <p>
                    1. <strong>DEFINITIONS.</strong> Capitalized terms used herein shall have the meanings set forth in
                    this
                    Section 1.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>1.1. Aggregated Data</strong>
                    means Personal Information and usage information that is
                    anonymized and aggregated with similar data and information to the extent that the
                    original Personal Information and usage information is no longer attributable to any
                    specific individual.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>1.2. Authorized Persons</strong>
                    means Provider’s employees, contractors, agents, and
                    auditors who have a need to know or otherwise access Personal Information to enable
                    Provider to perform its obligations under this Agreement, and who are bound by
                    con dentiality and other obligations su cient to protect Personal Information in
                    accordance with the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>1.3. Personal Information</strong>
                    means information that Customer provides or for which
                    Customer provides access to Provider, or information which Provider creates or obtains
                    on behalf of Customer, in accordance with this Agreement that: (i) directly or indirectly
                    identi es an individual; or (ii) can be used to authenticate an individual.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>1.4. Data Breach</strong>
                    means any act or omission that materially compromises the security,
                    con dentiality, or integrity of Personal Information or the physical, technical,
                    administrative, or organizational safeguards put in place by Provider, or by Customer
                    should Provider have access to Customer’s systems, that relate to the protection of the
                    security, con dentiality, or integrity of Personal Information, or (ii) receipt of a complaint
                    in relation to the privacy and data security practices of Service Provider or a breach or
                    alleged breach of this Agreement relating to such privacy and data security practices.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>1.5. Losses</strong>
                    mean all losses, damages, liabilities, de ciencies, actions, judgments,
                    interest, awards, penalties, nes, costs, or expenses of whatever kind, including
                    reasonable attorneys’ fees and the cost of enforcing any right to indemni cation
                    hereunder and the cost of pursuing any insurance providers.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.PERFORMANCE OF SERVICES.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.1. Services.</strong>
                    Provider will provide services (“Services”) and works, materials, or other
                    tangible or intangible property (“Deliverables”) to Customer in accordance with the terms
                    and conditions of this Agreement and one or more insertion orders (each an “Insertion
                    Order”) that may be agreed to and executed by the Parties, each of which will be made a
                    part of this Agreement and each of which will contain the applicable rates for the Services
                    and Deliverables set forth therein. This Agreement and any Insertion Orders entered into
                    hereunder constitute the entire agreement between the Parties concerning the subject
                    matter hereof and supersede any other prior or contemporaneous communications. In
                    the event of a con ict between the terms of this Agreement and any Insertion Order, the
                    terms of this Agreement will control unless the Insertion Order explicitly states otherwise.
                    The terms of any purchase order or any general terms and conditions Customer may
                    maintain will not apply. This Agreement does not obligate either Provider or Customer to
                    enter into any speci c Insertion Order or any Insertion Orders at all.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.2. Acceptance.</strong>
                    Except to the extent a Insertion Order contains speci c acceptance
                    provisions, all Services and/or Deliverables provided to Customer for approval will be
                    deemed accepted (“Accepted”) if within ten (10) days after delivery, Customer has not
                    provided to Provider written notice identifying speci cally any basis for not approving the
                    Services and/or Deliverables, as applicable.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.3. Correction/Re-Performance.</strong>
                    If a Service or Deliverable contains any
                    nonconformities, Customer shall describe to Provider in writing the issues with such
                    Service or Deliverable. Provider shall promptly and proactively correct the nonconformity
                    and redeliver the Service or Deliverable or re-perform the activities related to the Service
                    or Deliverable, as the case may be, unless Customer expressly states in writing that it
                    does not require Provider to correct a certain nonconformity that it considers, in
                    Customer’s sole discretion, to be immaterial.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.4. Change Orders.</strong>
                    Changes to the scope of the Services or any Deliverables shall be
                    made only in a writing executed by authorized representatives of both Parties. Provider
                    will not be obligated to work on a change until the Parties agree in writing upon its price
                    and/or schedule impact. Provider will continue performing the Services in according with
                    such Insertion Order until the Parties agree in writing to any such change or adjustment. If
                    the Parties are unable to agree to a mutually acceptable change or adjustment, either
                    Party may terminate the relevant Insertion Order upon ten (10) days’ written notice to the
                    other.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>2.5. Personnel; Subcontractors.</strong>
                    Provider reserves the right to determine which of its
                    personnel shall be assigned to perform Services; provided, however, that it will, subject to
                    scheduling and sta ng considerations, attempt to honor Customer’s request for speci c
                    individuals. Provider may use subcontractors to perform Services, in which case it will be
                    responsible for the performance of those subcontractors.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p>
                    <strong>3. CUSTOMER OBLIGATIONS.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>3.1. Cooperation.</strong>
                    Customer acknowledges that Provider’s ability to deliver the Services
                    depends upon full and timely cooperation by Customer and Customer’s sta , as well as
                    the timely access to and accuracy and completeness of any information provided.
                    Provider will have no liability for any delay in the provision of Services or other loss of any
                    nature resulting from any failure by Customer to provide full and timely cooperation or to
                    provide Provider accurate and complete information.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>3.2. Compliance with Laws.</strong>
                    Customer shall at all times comply with all federal, state,
                    and local laws, ordinances, regulations, and orders that are applicable to the operation of
                    its business and to this Agreement and its performance hereunder. Without limiting the
                    generality of the foregoing, Customer shall at all times, at its own expense, obtain and
                    maintain all certi cations, credentials, authorizations, licenses, and permits necessary to
                    conduct its business relating to the exercise of its rights and the performance of its
                    obligations under this Agreement. Customer is responsible for providing complete,
                    truthful, and legally compliant information to Provider, and Provider shall not be held
                    responsible for any non-compliance by Customer.
                </p>
                <strong>4. PAYMENT; FEES; EXPENSES.</strong>
                <p>
                    <strong>4.1. Fees.</strong>
                    As full and complete compensation for performing all Services speci ed in
                    this Agreement and for assuming all duties, responsibilities, and obligations required by
                    this Agreement, Customer will compensate Provider for all fees, compensation, and other
                    amounts as speci ed in the applicable Insertion Order (the “Fees”) in accordance with the
                    terms of this Agreement and in any Insertion Order entered into by the Parties. Fees are
                    exclusive of taxes, levies, duties, governmental charges and expenses (with the exception
                    of any Subcontractor’s income taxes), which amounts will be billed to and paid by
                    Customer.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>4.2. Expenses.</strong>Customer shall pay Provider for the reasonable expenses including,
                    but
                    not limited to, out of pocket travel and living expenses, incurred by Provider and its
                    personnel in connection with its performance of the Services (the “Expenses”).
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>4.3. Billing and Payment.</strong>
                    Provider shall prepare and submit invoices to the Customer
                    via email for all Services and expenses incurred on a monthly basis, or as otherwise set
                    forth in the Insertion Order. Customer will pay invoices in U.S. prior to the service start
                    date noted on Provider’s invoice. Payments due hereunder must be made by wire
                    transfer, certi ed check, bank check or such other method as may be agreed upon by the
                    Provider. Customer shall have no right of o set or withholding under this Agreement. Any
                    amounts not paid by Customer when due to Provider shall be subject to interest charges,
                    from the date due until paid, at the rate of one and one half percent (1.5%) per month, or
                    the highest interest rate allowable by law (whichever is less), payable monthly.
                    If any amounts due to Provider from Customer becomes past due for any reason,
                    Provider may at its option and without further notice withhold further Services until all
                    invoices have been paid in full, and such withholding of Services shall not be considered a
                    breach or default of any of Provider’s obligations under this Agreement.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p>
                    <strong>4.4. Taxes.</strong>
                    Provider is responsible for all Provider personnel and for the payment of
                    their compensation, including, if applicable, withholding of income taxes, and the
                    payment and withholding of social security and other payroll taxes, unemployment
                    insurance, workers’ compensation insurance payments, and disability bene ts. Customer
                    shall be responsible for all sales, use, and excise taxes, and any other similar taxes, duties,
                    and charges of any kind imposed by any federal, state, or local governmental entity on
                    any amounts payable by Customer hereunder.Any such taxes, duties, and charges currently assessed or
                    which may be assessed in the
                    future, that are applicable to the Services are for the Customer’s account, and Customer
                    hereby agrees to pay such taxes; provided, that, in no event shall Customer pay or be
                    responsible for any taxes imposed on, or with respect to, Provider’s income, revenues,
                    gross receipts, personnel, or real or personal property or other assets.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>4.5. Disputes.</strong>
                    In the event of any good faith dispute with regard to a portion of an
                    invoice, the undisputed portion shall be paid as provided herein. Upon resolution of the
                    disputed portion, any amounts owed to Provider shall be paid with interest at the rate set
                    forth below accruing from the date such amounts were originally due.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>5. CONFIDENTIALITY.</strong>
                    From time to time during the Term of this Agreement, either Party
                    (as the “Disclosing Party”) may disclose or make available to the other Party (as the
                    “Receiving Party”) information about its business a airs, products/services, con dential
                    intellectual property, trade secrets, third-party con dential information and other
                    sensitive or proprietary information, whether orally or in written, electronic or other form
                    or media, and whether or not marked, designated or otherwise identi ed as “con dential”
                    (collectively, “Con dential Information”). Con dential Information shall not include
                    information that, at the time of disclosure: (i) is or becomes generally available to and
                    known by the public other than as a result of, directly or indirectly, any breach of this
                    Section 5 by the Receiving Party or any of its representatives; (ii) is or becomes available to
                    the Receiving Party on a non-con dential basis from a third-party source, provided that
                    such third party is not and was not prohibited from disclosing such Con dential
                    Information; (iii) was known by or in the possession of the Receiving Party or its
                    representatives before being disclosed by or on behalf of the Disclosing Party; (iv) was or
                    is independently developed by the Receiving Party without reference to or use, in whole
                    or in part, of any of the Disclosing Party’s Con dential Information; or (v) is required to be
                    disclosed under applicable federal, state or local law, regulation or a valid order issued by
                    a court or governmental agency of competent jurisdiction. The Receiving Party shall: (A)
                    protect and safeguard the con dentiality of the Disclosing Party’s Con dential
                    Information with at least the same degree of care as the Receiving Party would protect its
                    own Con dential Information, but in no event with less than a commercially reasonable
                    degree of care; (B) not use the Disclosing Party’s Con dential Information, or permit it to
                    be accessed or used, for any purpose other than to exercise its rights or perform its
                    obligations under this Agreement; and (C) not disclose any such Con dential Information
                    to any person or entity, except to the Receiving Party’s representatives who need to know
                    the Con dential Information to assist the Receiving Party, or act on its behalf, to exercise
                    its rights or perform its obligations under the Agreement.
                    The Receiving Party shall be responsible for any breach of this Section 5 caused by any of
                    its representatives. At any time during or after the term of this Agreement, at the
                    Disclosing Party’s written request, the Receiving Party shall promptly return, and shall
                    require its representatives to return to the Disclosing Party all copies, whether in written,
                    electronic or other form or media, of the Disclosing Party’s Con dential Information, or
                    destroy all such copies and certify in writing to the Disclosing Party that such Con dential
                    Information has been destroyed. In addition to all other remedies available at law, the
                    Disclosing Party may seek equitable relief (including injunctive relief) against the Receiving
                    Party and its representatives to prevent the breach or threatened breach of this Section 5
                    and to secure its enforcement.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p>
                    <strong>6. INTELLECTUAL PROPRIETARY RIGHTS.</strong>
                    All intellectual property rights, including
                    copyrights, patents, patent disclosures and inventions (whether patentable or not),
                    trademarks, service marks, trade secrets, know-how and other con dential information,
                    trade dress, trade names, logos, corporate names and domain names, together with all of
                    the goodwill associated therewith, derivative works and all other rights (collectively,
                    “Intellectual Property Rights”) in and to all the Deliverables), except for any Con dential
                    Information of Customer or customer materials, shall be owned by Provider. Provider
                    hereby grants Customer a license to use all Intellectual Property Rights in the Deliverables
                    free of additional charge and on a non-exclusive, worldwide, non-transferable, non-
                    sublicensable, fully paid-up, royalty-free and perpetual basis to the extent necessary to
                    enable Customer to make reasonable use of the Deliverables and the Services.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>7. INFORMATION SECURITY.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>7.1. Compliance with Laws.</strong>
                    Provider will comply with applicable laws and regulations in
                    its creation, collection, receipt, access, use, storage, disposal, and disclosure of Personal
                    Information.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>7.2. Security Measures.</strong>
                    Provider will employ reasonable security measures to protect
                    Personal Information in accordance with Provider’s information security policy as
                    amended from time to time.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>7.3. Cyber Incident Response Plan.</strong>
                    Provider maintains a cyber-incident breach
                    response plan in accordance with accepted industry standards and will implement the
                    procedures required under such plan on the occurrence of a Data Breach.
                    7.4. Noti cation. Provider will notify Customer of a Data Breach as soon as reasonably
                    practicable, but no later than fourteen (14), after Provider becomes aware of it.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>7.5. Return or Disposal of Personal Information.</strong>
                    On the termination or expiration of
                    this Agreement, Provider will promptly return to Customer or securely dispose of all
                    Personal Information in its possession. If Provider is not reasonably able to return or
                    securely dispose of Personal Information, including, but not limited to, Personal
                    Information stored on backup media, Provider will continue to protect such Personal
                    Information in accordance with the terms of this Agreement until such time that it can
                    reasonably return or securely dispose of such Personal Information.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>7.6. Aggregated Data.</strong>
                    Provider shall own all right, title, and interest in the Aggregated
                    Data.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>8. LIMITED WARRANTIES AND REMEDIES.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>8.1. Professionalism.</strong>
                    Provider warrants that all Services will be performed using
                    generally accepted industry standards and practices and that the Services and
                    Deliverables will not knowingly violate or infringe any third party’s intellectual property
                    rights.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>8.2. Exclusions.</strong>
                    Provider will not be liable for any services or products provided by
                    third-party vendors, developers, or consultants identi ed or referred to Customer by
                    Provider or its employees, a liates, or agents, unless such third-party products or
                    services are provided under written agreement between Provider and Customer, and
                    then only to the extent expressly provided in such agreement.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p>
                    <strong>8.3. Disclaimers.</strong>
                    EXCEPT FOR THE EXPRESS WARRANTIES SPECIFIED IN THIS SECTION 8,
                    CUSTOMER ACCEPTS THE SERVICES AND DELIVERABLES “AS IS”. THE WARRANTIES AND
                    REMEDIES SET FORTH IN THIS SECTION 8 ARE EXCLUSIVE AND IN LIEU OF ALL OTHER
                    WARRANTIES OF PROVIDER AND REMEDIES OF CUSTOMER, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, ARISING
                    BY LAW OR OTHERWISE, WITH RESPECT TO ANY ERROR, DEFECT, DEFICIENCY OR
                    NONCOMPLIANCE IN ANY SERVICES, DELIVERABLES, PRE-EXISTING WORKS OR OTHER
                    ITEMS FURNISHED BY OR ON BEHALF OF PROVIDER UNDER THIS AGREEMENT OR ANY
                    STATEMENTS OF WORK, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY OF
                    MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, QUALITY, ACCURACY, OR NON-
                    INFRINGEMENT AND ANY IMPLIED WARRANTY ARISING FROM COURSE OF
                    PERFORMANCE, COURSE OF DEALING OR USAGE OF TRADE.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>9. INDEMNIFICATION.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>9.1. By Provider.</strong>
                    Provider shall defend, indemnify, and hold harmless Customer and its
                    officers, directors, employees, agents, successors, and permitted assigns (each, a
                    “Customer Indemnitee”) from and against all Losses arising out of or resulting from: (a)
                    bodily injury, death of any person, or damage to real or tangible, personal property
                    resulting from the willful, fraudulent, or grossly negligent acts or omissions of Provider
                    or Provider Personnel; (b) Provider’s material breach of any representation, warranty, or
                    obligation of Provider set forth in this Agreement; or (c) a claim that any of the Services or
                    Deliverables or Customer’s receipt or use thereof infringes any intellectual property right
                    of a third party arising under the laws of the United States. However, Provider shall have
                    no obligations under this Section 9.1 with respect to intellectual property rights claims to
                    the extent arising out of: (a) any instruction, information, designs, speci cations, or other
                    materials provided by Customer in writing to Provider; (b) use of the Deliverables in
                    combination with any materials not supplied to Customer or speci ed by Provider in
                    writing, if the infringement would have been avoided by the use of the Deliverables not so
                    combined; or (c) any modi cations or changes made to the Deliverables by or on behalf of
                    any person other than Provider or its personnel.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>9.2. Customer’s Indemnification.</strong>
                    Customer shall defend, indemnify, and hold
                    harmless Provider and its officers, directors, employees, agents, successors, and
                    permitted assigns from and against all Losses arising out of or resulting from: (a) bodily
                    injury, death of any person, or damage to real or tangible, personal property resulting
                    from the grossly negligent or willful acts or omissions of Customer; and (b) Customer’s
                    material breach of any representation, warranty, or obligation of Customer in
                    this Agreement.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>9.3. Indemnification cation Procedure.</strong>
                    The party seeking indemnification hereunder shall
                    promptly notify the indemnifying party in writing of any claim and cooperate with the
                    indemnifying party at the indemnifying party’s sole cost and expense. The indemnifying
                    party shall immediately take control of the defense and investigation of such claim and
                    shall employ counsel of its choice to handle and defend the same, at the indemnifying
                    party’s sole cost and expense. The indemnifying party shall not settle any action in a
                    manner that adversely affects the rights of the indemni ed party without the indemni ed
                    party’s prior written consent, which shall not be unreasonably withheld or delayed. The
                    indemni ed party may participate in and observe the proceedings at its own cost and
                    expense
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p>
                    <strong>9.4. Obligation Exceptions.</strong>
                    Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Agreement,
                    the indemnifying party is not obligated to indemnify, hold harmless, or defend the
                    indemni ed party against any claim (whether direct or indirect) to the extent such claim
                    or corresponding losses arise out of or result from, in whole or in part, the indemni ed
                    party’s: (a) negligence or more culpable act or omission (including recklessness or willful
                    misconduct); or (b) bad faith failure to materially comply with any of its obligations set
                    forth in this Agreement.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>10. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>10.1. Dollar Cap.</strong>
                    Except for the specific remedies expressly identified as such in this
                    Agreement, Provider’s sole liability (whether in contract, tort, negligence, strict liability in
                    tort or by statute or otherwise) for any claim in any manner related to this Agreement,
                    shall be the payment of direct damages, and such damages shall in no event in the
                    aggregate exceed the Fees and Expenses received by Provider hereunder with respect to
                    the work involved under the applicable Insertion Order. Customer’s exclusive remedy for
                    any claim arising out of these arrangements shall be for Provider, upon receipt of written
                    notice pursuant to Section 14.7, to use commercially reasonable e orts to cure the breach
                    at its expense, or failing that, the return of Fees and Expenses paid to Provider for the
                    work related to the breach.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>10.2. Exclusion of Consequential Damages.</strong>
                    IN NO EVENT SHALL EITHER PARTY BE
                    LIABLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR PUNITIVE
                    DAMAGE, LOSS OR EXPENSES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, BUSINESS
                    INTERRUPTION, LOST BUSINESS, LOST PROFITS, OR LOST SAVINGS), EVEN IF IT HAS BEEN
                    ADVISED OF THEIR POSSIBLE EXISTENCE. THE LIABILITIES LIMITED BY THIS SECTION 10
                    APPLY: (A) TO LIABILITY FOR NEGLIGENCE; (B) REGARDLESS OF THE FORM OF ACTION,
                    WHETHER IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT PRODUCT LIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE; (C) EVEN IF A
                    PARTY IS ADVISED IN ADVANCE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF THE DAMAGES IN QUESTION AND
                    EVEN IF SUCH DAMAGES WERE FORESEEABLE; AND (D) EVEN IF A PARTY’S REMEDIES FAIL
                    OF THEIR ESSENTIAL PURPOSE.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>11. TERM AND TERMINATION.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>11.1. Term.</strong>
                    This Agreement shall commence on the Effective Date and continue until
                    otherwise terminated under this Section 11 (the “Term”).
                </p>

                <p>
                    <strong>11.2. Termination for Breach.</strong>
                    Either Party may terminate this Agreement at any time in
                    the event of a breach by the other Party of a material covenant, representation, warranty,
                    commitment, or obligation under this Agreement that remains uncured for thirty (30)
                    days following written notice thereof. Such termination shall be e ective immediately and
                    automatically upon the expiration of the applicable notice period, without further notice
                    or action by either Party. Termination shall be in addition to any other remedies that may
                    be available to the non-breaching Party. Notwithstanding the foregoing, any failure by
                    Customer to timely pay Provider any amounts due under any Insertion Order will
                    constitute a material breach of this Agreement.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>

                <p>
                    <strong>11.3. Termination for Bankruptcy, Insolvency, or Financial Insecurity.</strong>
                    Either Party may
                    terminate this Agreement immediately at its option upon written notice if the other Party:
                    (a) becomes or is declared insolvent or bankrupt; (b) is the subject of a voluntary or
                    involuntary bankruptcy or other proceeding related to its liquidation or solvency, which
                    proceeding is not dismissed within ninety (90) calendar days after its ling; (c) ceases to do
                    business in the normal course; or (d) makes an assignment for the bene t of creditors.
                    This Agreement shall terminate immediately and automatically upon any determination
                    by a court of competent jurisdiction that either Party is excused or prohibited from
                    performing in full all obligations hereunder, including, without limitation, rejection of this
                    Agreement pursuant to 11 U.S.C. §365.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>11.4. Obligations Upon Termination.</strong>
                    If this Agreement or any Insertion Order is
                    terminated pursuant to this Section 11, then, unless otherwise speci cally provided for in
                    the Agreement or the applicable Insertion Order, the following will apply: (a) the parties
                    will cooperate to e ect an orderly, effcient, effective and expeditious termination of the
                    party’s respective activities under the terminated Insertion Order; (b) Provider will return
                    to Customer any and all customer-furnished items delivered by Customer to Provider
                    under the terminated Insertion Order; (c) Provider will have no obligation to perform any
                    Services under the terminated Insertion Order after the effective date of the termination;
                    and (d) Customer will pay to Provider any Fees, reimbursable Expenses, compensation or
                    other amounts payable for Services performed under the terminated Insertion Order
                    prior to the effective date of the termination. Upon termination, each Party shall return
                    the other party’s Confidential Information and any other materials or property of the
                    other Party that is in its possession at the time of termination.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>12. DISPUTE RESOLUTION.</strong>
                    The Parties agree that, in the event of a dispute or alleged
                    breach, they will work together in good faith rst, to resolve the matter internally by
                    escalating it to higher levels of management and, then if necessary, to use a mutually
                    agreed upon alternative dispute resolution technique prior to resorting to litigation. Any
                    mediation or arbitration under this Section 12 will be held in Seattle, Washington. In the
                    event the parties fail to mutually agree upon such technique within thirty (30) days after
                    good faith attempts at internal resolution have failed, either party may resort to litigation.
                    This provision shall not apply to disputes involving con dentiality or infringement of
                    intellectual property rights (in which case either party shall be free to seek any available
                    remedies).
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>13. NON-SOLICITATION.</strong>
                    Customer will not directly or indirectly solicit any employee of
                    Provider during the Term and for a period of 12 months after its completion, except with
                    the prior written consent of Provider.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>14. MISCELLANEOUS.</strong>
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>14.1. Severability.</strong>
                    If a court holds any provision of this Agreement to be illegal, invalid,
                    or unenforceable, the remaining provisions will remain in full force and e ect and the
                    Parties will amend the Agreement to give e ect to the stricken clause to the maximum
                    extent possible.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>14.2. Relationship of the Parties.</strong>
                    The relationship between the Parties is that of
                    independent contractors. Nothing contained in this Agreement shall be construed as
                    creating any agency, partnership, joint venture, or other form of joint enterprise,
                    employment, or duciary relationship between the Parties, and neither party shall have
                    authority to contract for or bind the other Party in any manner whatsoever.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <p>
                    <strong>14.3. Assignment.</strong>
                    Neither Party may assign this Agreement or any Insertion Order
                    without the written consent of the other. Any attempt by a Party to this Agreement to
                    assign this Agreement or any Insertion Order without the written consent of the other
                    Party may be deemed notice of termination of this Agreement, e ective on the date of
                    assignment, by the other Party.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>14.4. Waiver.</strong>
                    A Party does not waive any right under this Agreement by failing to insist
                    on compliance with any of the terms of this Agreement or by failing to exercise any right
                    hereunder. Any waivers granted hereunder are e ective only if recorded in a writing
                    signed by the Party granting such waiver.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>14.5. Force Majeure.</strong>
                    The Provider shall not be liable or responsible to Customer, nor be
                    deemed to have defaulted or breached this Agreement, for any failure or delay in ful lling
                    or performing any term of this Agreement when and to the extent such failure or delay is
                    caused by or results from acts or circumstances beyond the reasonable control of
                    Provider including, without limitation, acts of God, ood, re, earthquake, explosion,
                    governmental actions, war, invasion or hostilities (whether war is declared or not),
                    terrorist threats or acts, riot, or other civil unrest, national emergency, revolution,
                    insurrection, epidemic, lock-outs, strikes or other labor disputes (whether or not relating
                    to either party's workforce), or restraints or delays a ecting carriers or inability or delay in
                    obtaining supplies of adequate or suitable materials, materials or telecommunication
                    breakdown or power outage, provided that, if the event in question continues for a
                    continuous period in excess of 90 days, Customer shall be entitled to give notice in writing
                    to Provider to terminate this Agreement.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>14.6. Governing Law; Venue.</strong>
                    This Agreement is governed by Washington law, excluding
                    its con icts of law rules, except to the extent that such law is preempted by applicable
                    federal law. The Parties hereby irrevocably submit to exclusive personal jurisdiction and
                    venue in the federal and state courts in King County, Washington, for any dispute arising
                    out of this Agreement, waive all objections to jurisdiction and venue of such courts, and
                    agree not to commence or prosecute any such dispute other than in such courts.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>14.7. Notice.</strong>
                    All notices, requests, consents, claims, demands, waivers, and other
                    communications hereunder (each, a “Notice”) must be in writing and addressed to the
                    Parties at the addresses set forth on the Insertion Order(s) (or to such other address that
                    may be designated by the Party giving Notice from time to time in accordance with this
                    Section). All Notices must be delivered by personal delivery, nationally recognized
                    overnight courier (with all fees pre-paid), or email (with con rmation of transmission) or
                    certi ed or registered mail (in each case, return receipt requested, postage pre-paid).
                    Except as otherwise provided in this Agreement, a Notice is e ective only: (a) upon receipt
                    by the receiving Party; and (b) if the Party giving the Notice has complied with the
                    requirements of this Section.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <strong>14.8. Cumulative Rights;</strong>
                    Construction; Amendment; Counterparts. The rights and
                    remedies of the Parties under this Agreement are cumulative, and either Party may
                    enforce any of its rights or remedies under this Agreement or other rights and remedies
                    available to it at law or in equity. No modi cation or amendment of this Agreement is
                    binding unless it is in writing and signed by both Parties. This Agreement may be executed
                    by electronic or digital means and in counterparts, each of which (including signature
                    pages) will be deemed an original, but all of which together will constitute one and the
                    same instrument. Each person who signs this Agreement on behalf of a Party represents
                    and warrants that he or she has the authority to enter into this Agreement on behalf of
                    the Party and bind the Party in accordance with its terms.
                </p>
                <p style="page-break-after: always;"/>
                <div style="border:1px solid black;">
                    <p style="text-align:center;border-style: solid;">
                        Terms of Service:
                        <p style="">
                            Fees based upon minimum guaranteed 6 months – 6 month initial commitment from date of
                            launch.
                            Agreement will renew annually for additional 6 months unless otherwise noted. Advertiser or
                            Provider may
                            cancel this agreement by providing 30 day written notice (including notice through email) at
                            the
                            time that
                            initial contracted term is ful lled. All elements of the campaign must be pre-paid in full
                            each
                            month for the
                            campaign to run. If payment lapses, the campaign will be paused until payment is received.
                            Prices include
                            creative (two rounds of initial design, changes as needed (ads should run for at least 30
                            days
                            without
                            changes), campaign management and monthly reports. Branded Search Targeting packages include
                            both
                            desktop and mobile investments. Search management fee is $400 or 20%, whichever is greater.
                            Targeted
                            Online Display CPM is $12, with premium placement, $18
                        </p>
                    </p>
                </div>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>

    <template id="report_contract_clx">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="doc">
                <t t-call="clx_invoice_reports.report_clx_contract_document" t-lang="doc.partner_id.lang"/>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>
